hairlosstreatmentstip.com 2015-11-17

# Privacy - Hair Loss Treatment

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of the site. Privacy of our visitors is very important to us. Hairlosstreatmentstip is a blog where you can find different things about hair treatments and hair styles. We do not record any private information about our readers, we only record IP address.

### Security:

The security of your personal information is very important to us, but remember no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information. We cannot guarantee its absolutely safe.

### Information Collection:

All the information and tips given on our site is collected from internet and some other useful sources.

### Cookies:

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored in your computer’s hard drive. Like many sites we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

### Links to other site:

Our site may contain links to other sites that are not operate by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to the third party site. So, we strongly advice you to review our privacy policy of every site you visit.

Hairlosstreatmentstip has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policy or practices of any third person sites or services.

### Changes to This Privacy policy:

Hair loss treatments tip site will update policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new privacy policy on this site. You are advice to review this privacy policy periodically for any changes.

### Contact Us:

If you have any question about this privacy policy You can [contact us](http://hairlosstreatmentstip.com/contact-us).
